brazenwoman.com 2014-11-29

# Privacy Policy - BrazenWoman

**Our Privacy Policy**  
At BrazenWoman, we are committed to protecting your privacy, and maintain a general policy of openness about how we collect, use and disclose your personal information.

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you about BrazenWoman’s practices relating to the collection, use, disclosure and protection of personal information that may be provided through access to or use of our website, services and publications, or that may otherwise be collected by us.  BY SUBSCRIBING TO OUR POSTS (or future newsletters) OR USING OUR WEBSITE (the “Site”), YOU CONSENT TO THE COLLECTION, USE AND DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION (AS DEFINED BELOW) IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE FOLLOWING TERMS AND CONDITIONS.

This Privacy Policy also explains how you can contact us if you have a question about, want to make a change to or want to delete any personal information that BrazenWoman may be maintaining about you.  We strongly recommend that you take the time to read this Privacy Policy and retain it for future reference.

**What Personal Information We Collect  **  
For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, and in accordance with Canadian privacy legislation, “personal information” is generally defined as information about an identifiable individual, or information that allows an individual to be identified.  
The personal information collected by BrazenWoman upon subscription to blog updates may include at least some of the following:

  * Contact information, including name and e-mail address

When you provide us with your personal information, we will inform you as to why we are collecting it.

From time to time, we may ask you to provide us with more detailed information regarding your interests in order to serve you better and understand what topics may be of interest to you.  It will be entirely up to you as to whether you choose to share this information with us.

Also, if you send us an e-mail message, we may retain that message and your e-mail address, as well as any response we send you.

**How We Use Your Personal Information**

We use your personal information to:

  * Provide you with updates on our current content as it is published;
  * Provide you with personalized services and interactive communication (which may include, in the future, an e-mail newsletter and / or e-mails we may send on behalf of sponsors);
  * Research, develop, manage, protect and improve those communications;
  * Advise you about new products and services that may be of interest to you; and
  * Develop and maintain our relationship with you and communicate with you.

In addition, from time to time, we may use your personal information for the following purposes:

  * to detect and protect BrazenWoman and third parties against error, fraud, theft and other illegal activity, and to audit compliance with BrazenWoman’s policies and contractual obligations;
  * to understand your needs and preferences, including to contact and communicate with you and to conduct surveys, research and evaluations;
  * for any other purpose we may indicate to you from time to time.

**When We Disclose Your Personal Information**  
We will not sell, license, trade or rent your personal information to or with others.

**BrazenWoman** may share personal information with third parties engaged to assist us in providing services (including but not limited to software development, website development and hosting, data processing, document management and office administration) to you or to carry out one or more of the purposes described above.  These service providers are prohibited from using your personal information for any purpose other than to provide this assistance and are required to protect personal information disclosed by  **BrazenWoman**  and to comply with the general privacy principles describes in this Privacy Policy.

**BrazenWoman**  reserves the right to disclose personal information to a third party if a law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena or court order legally requires or authorizes us to do so.

**BrazenWoman**  also reserves the right to disclose and/or transfer personal information to a third party in the event of a proposed or actual purchase, sale (including a liquidation, realization, foreclosure or repossession), lease, merger, amalgamation or any other type of acquisition, disposal, transfer, conveyance or financing of all or any portion of  **BrazenWoman**  or of any of the business or assets or shares of  **BrazenWoman**  or a division thereof in order for you to continue to receive the same products and services from the third party.

**Knowledge and Consent**

**BrazenWoman**  COLLECTS PERSONAL INFORMATION ABOUT YOU ONLY WHEN YOU VOLUNTARILY PROVIDE IT.  Typically, we will seek consent for the use or disclosure of your personal information at the time of collection.  In certain circumstances, consent may be sought after the information has been collected but before use (for example, when we want to use information for a purpose not previously identified).

The form of consent that we seek, including whether it is express or implied, will largely depend on the sensitivity of the personal information and the reasonable expectations of the individual in the circumstances.

You may withdraw consent at any time, subject to legal or contractual restrictions and reasonable notice.  If you wish to withdraw your consent at any time, please contact us at BrazenEditors@gmail.com

We will not, as a condition of the supply of a product or service, require you to consent to the collection, use or disclosure of information beyond that required to fulfill the explicitly specified and legitimate purposes for which the information is being provided.

**Use or Disclosure for Marketing, Advertising and Sponsorship Purposes**  
We may also use (but will not disclose) your personal information to promote and market additional goods, services and special offers from us, our affiliates and sponsors, including by means of direct marketing.  To ensure advertisers understand who our subscribers are and what they are interested in, we will compile your information and create general profiles of our subscribers’ demographic information and interests.  However, we will never share any PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE information with our advertisers.

**How We Protect Your Personal Information**.  
**BrazenWoman**  makes all commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that personal information collected from you is protected against loss and unauthorized access.  This protection applies in relation to information stored in both electronic and hard-copy form.  Access to your personal information is restricted to selected employees or representatives.  In addition, BrazenWoman employs robust information security techniques to protect personal information against loss and unauthorized access.

**Links to Third-Party Sites**  
This website may offer links to other third-party websites for your convenience.  You should be aware that operators of linked websites may also collect your personal information (including information generated through the use of cookies) when you link to their websites.  BrazenWoman is not responsible for how such third parties collect, use or disclose your personal information so it is important to familiarize yourself with their privacy policies, which may differ from ours, before providing them with your personal information.  BrazenWoman cannot be held liable for your use of such third-party websites.

**Retention of Your Personal Information**  
**BrazenWoman**  retains your personal information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purpose(s) for which it was collected and to comply with applicable laws.  When that need has ended, your personal information will be removed from our system and destroyed in a manner that ensures your security.

**Control Of Your Personal Information**  
We want you to be able to maintain control over how we use your personal information.  You will always have the option to instruct us not to use your name, e-mail, or any other information. beyond providing you with the service or information you requested.  Additionally, e-mail communications will always include an identification of the sender and an “Unsubscribe” option.  Should you wish to unsubscribe at any time, you may instruct us to immediately do so by clicking on the link.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
**BrazenWoman**  reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at anytime without notice. The Privacy Policy posted at any time or from time to time via this Site shall be deemed to be the Privacy Policy then in effect.

**Access to, Correcting or Updating Your Information**  
If you request access to your personal information, subject to certain exceptions, BrazenWoman will inform you of the existence, use and disclosure of your personal information and will provide you with a summary of that information. If we can’t provide you access to your personal information, we will provide an explanation.

You can help us maintain the accuracy of your personal information by notifying us of any changes to this information.  You may contact us in any one of the following ways to request access to or correction or update of your personal information:

E-mail: brazeneditors@gmail.com  
Telephone: 416-939-2113

**Contacting Us**  
If you have any questions or requests about this Privacy Policy or if you have reason to believe that  we may have failed to adhere to this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at BrazenEditors@gmail.com or call us at 416-939-2113

This Privacy Policy is intended to comply with the provisions of the [Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act](http://www.privcom.gc.ca/legislation/02_06_01_e.asp "Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act") (Canada).
